[Music]
[Laughter]
welcome again to the natatorium today we
have individual medals as the ultimate
prize for men and women at the classic
heights of three and ten meters to look
forward to plus we conclude with an
innovative team event which will combine
men and women's springboard and platform
more of that later but we start with the
women up on that 10 metre platform well
occurs once all China has every right to
host at the very highest level it's
certainly diving just confirming today's
program for you a preliminary followed
by the final event later today
of course the origins of the sport can
be traced back to this country to a
thousand years ago but now in the 21st
century China dominates the sport at
Olympic and World Championship level can
they signpost an extension of their
goals in the era over the next few days
with a clean sweep of the titles here at
the Youth Olympic Games 17 other
countries will be trying to do something
about that
encouraging proud to see this first
preliminary session grounds expected to
build as week
the days of competitions let me explain
them a bit about the format here the
qualification process from the diving
here in Nanjing is a little involved
FINA held an official qualifying
competition in March in Guadalajara in
Mexico the top nine divers in each event
one qualified places for these games for
their country and not just for
themselves so a number of the divers
from that competition are not here but
their countries are still representing
than the hosts Charlotte was guaranteed
a place of course and there were two
more universality places which could be
offered for example if this event the
extra place was granted to Canada who
are of course extremely strong in
women's diving the format is also a
little different eight dives for the
women today at 10 meter for dives with a
total degree of difficulty heading up to
no more than 7.6
just saying here the divers who will be
getting us underway this morning each of
them with 8 dives these dives are chosen
from four specified routes then there
are four more times without any degree
of difficulty limits where the divers
have a free rein to show us what they
can do these are also drawn from a range
of groups it does sound a little bit
complicated but don't worry too much
about the technicalities just sit back
and enjoy the show one other difference
I should just point out which will help
to make the small eagle even more
competitive the marks when the first
four dives those are the ones of the
limited category are carried into the
final where as usual the divers will
complete in reverse order for how they
finish in these preliminaries I'll take
you through that again as the
competition involves
your on-screen graphics will explain
that how the story and everything works
quite clearly as I said you can just
Marvel up what is likely to be a very
high standard competition diving very
much a young person sport so you really
can expect from terrific standards here
final note of the judging of course
judges allocate points out of ten in
half a point the grades each time is
allocated a degree of difficulty seven
judges the top two marks the lowest two
marks are all discarded and the middle
three marks are then multiplied by the
degree of difficulty back to you your
points score
China absolutely dominated as they do in
so many international competitions in
these first Youth Olympic Games four
years ago in Singapore clean sweep when
there were just four events then within
three in ten
that's often tend to do very marriage
that the clean sweet so the diving
competition here in Nanjing finally gets
underway these competitors will be so
keen to get into that pool gathered
press na slick from Ukraine will get us
underway the forward one and a half
somersault
these early dives have quite a low
degree of difficulty so it's all about
the execution
she will be quite high to be so we
really have to make sure they get the
dive as flawless as possible the tariffs
on gammas openly died there's only one
point six seven point five scooter 36
points
simple duck raesha Layden Mahoney from
the United States she's 18 years of age
she opens in the forward one and a half
somersault in the piked position
[Applause]
now the coaches will be breaking down
the dive into its different stages take
off the various positions through the
die and of course that entry position
which although it isn't everything is
important because it does tend to leave
that final impression on the judges
ratio there in 2/7 and a 7.5 34 40
great day hold up
on the throgs at the qualifying event in
Mexico the girl from Brazil 18 years of
age and she is one of the more favored
divers in this competition she opens
with a forward one and a half somersault
piked
[Applause]
a nice relaxed opening died
Kayne's together they're punching a hole
through the water 7.5 36 there won't be
a big difference in these scores with
the low tariff dives it has the
competition I'd rather sleep things will
change the arena Fichtner is next from
Belarus she's just 16 years of age
forward 1/2 somersault piked 1.6
they said it's all about execution then
you can't really afford to make to the
leak significant mistakes with these
opening dives
Serena needed getting the entry as she
would have wanted her school down among
the 60s there 2880
so I can indeed Perez Belton I'm from
Colombia
he's just 17 years of age she has a
forward 1/2 somersault point
privacy
nice relaxed remember that we get the
benefit of those replays the juggies
don't they have to hit their mark the
button straight away three 7s in the
third in 360
Molly Carlson from Canada she's the
youngest over here in at 9 G it would
one the health service or
16 - next week
like scepter these girls competing on
the 3-meter springboard
[Music]
a little bit untidy 1/8 following stages
36.5 31:20
well you can ping
applause ripples around this arena for
Chinese young diver not expected as ever
of every Chinese diver
when he does coach like six and come
here almost the success of the dive and
especially when you get to the bigger
competitors in the moments and that rip
they talk about very elegantly nice
position out to punching the hole so up
right in the entry into the water there
straight to the top of the pile 40
points there in Champagne putting down a
very early marker
this is those yee-hoo what experienced
Malaysian diver competed at the
Commonwealth Games variety and the
experience of these
[Applause]
[Music]
very fluidly slight in five four three
three seven kilograms having three
powers notified 20
nervously discrepancy some of the box
that shows that this is a sport about
opinion
get quarter range barra funda from Egypt
another 16 year old is saying forward
one and a half somersault
just holding the way there in the entry
the legs book really held all the way
through that guy and so the rocks down
over 65s 31 20
letting cannot be from frogs 17 years of
age Formica painting
[Applause]
because in the 10-meter qualifying event
in Mexico
Joey phone reception position held all
the way through into the water
now the judge is of course of what they
think and they liked it as well
some ate the Hogs in their 39:20 very
good start for me meant to go
and I fabula are off the law sir is on
paper the girl most likely to challenge
a Chinese supremacy here she is an
established international diver with a
full Olympic silver medal in the Tim
Eaton synchronized event with the highly
regarded Paola Espinosa of Mexico Mexico
a real powerhouse of diving with
international level a great tradition
went back to those clips Allah acapulco
but 3360 was not a blazing star for her
now this will be pleased to just got
that feel of the watering competition
for the first time it's straight away
blue champagne goes to the top of the
pack but it is very early this
competition but remember these marks
will count later
[Applause]
[Music]
round 2 of 8 remember gang out close
know slick from Ukraine and create
getting success of international levels
as well invent and winning competition
in with one the half solar self hiked
2.0
matera here
losing herself at the top of the dive
judges will look for how tight that Pike
position is tied right up onto the knees
bent position there from the Ukrainian
but again a good straight entry pulled
right to the water 26 points
pressure laden Mahoney 2012 world junior
champion at 3 meters competing in both
events here in Nanjing it would one and
a half somersault piked
for the young American
[Music]
slightly more successful on the
springboard of the platform when she's
competed in the World Series and abroad
three events in the feeder program and
she has got 43 points from her second
guy
now good day on the theatre of Brazil 80
years of age
[Music]
Walter there
just to continue the rotation their
colleagues Thank You Polly
see arena pizza of Belarus
and second to the European Junior
Championships last year won the hot
Summer Sun is the dahle idea remember
is a positional entry
little heavy
[Music]
you can see that the live the legs away
to the perpendicular and that could be
squash people always they were just 33
points
Santa Catalina Perez belted out from
Columbia again a country with weather
strong deliver the presents
internationally didn't compete at the
qualifying event
put into the entry position she would
have wanted there
again you can see for this angle just
falling away from the vertical there
and 31 points not a great return from
her second day
when he cars moving dive look really
sitting her on the way she would have
wanted the girl from Thunder Bay in
Ontario 16 next month
trusting character the all the Canadian
dials especially the girls come from
Quebec based in Montreal she's not a bit
of a live out there in Thunder Bay is
Ontario mister work for the coach there
under the direction from the
International coaches back in Quebec
that's tidier gone Bali three sevens
giving her 42 points
[Music]
don't we need more divers in the feeder
world rankings
[Applause]
responding there quite predictably
it's gonna be until we get to the latter
dives that we'll really see her showing
her best butt so hard to pick faults in
that lovely relaxed clean entry hardly a
ripple oh yes
54 points three nines just to see just
what standard the judge is set really on
this the opening competition well
they're going to be keen to dole out
those nines and tens which need to be
earned but do get the crowd going
Malaysia too has become quite a force in
world diving her hero is of course panda
Laila Ali long time
we won two silvers four years ago in
Singapore and then went on to become a
real star in Malaysia first female
Olympic medallist and Elena that's her
heroin and to 8008 is a very good score
indeed
aha
we shall see how they go as Matar
abdel-salam as well to say girl the Duke
competed Lee qualified competition of 16
her coach and she's he said sorry but
she was only able to go to complete the
qualifying event because she finished
her exams the educational standards are
very strict indeed Pike position there
in Egypt and it's not easy for them to
combine the training with the education
standards only four points there for
Baha
la cara de
from France teaching in the laundry in
Colorado earlier this year to give her a
first taste of international competition
[Applause]
sound of the guys there
we relaxed
the position held by the way through the
entry
judges liked it as well 50 points that's
a very good encouragement there
I've counted off goal offer really
getting off to the flying start
[Applause]
don't you look heavy there okay
the powerful that I've uh compared to
the extremely slender Chinese girl for
example that's a very well held entry
there though really tight control of her
core strength three 8:48 is a little bit
more what we would have been expecting
two rounds of the competition then we'll
shake pain really setting the standards
but to the French girl really doing very
well indeed still waiting for the other
established stars to make a bit of a
show that very much early stages here
[Music]
on to round 3 trading coach they're
watching for got a logic fact I've hiked
the Terra kyary's
1.8
80 year olds point wanted good degree of
experience to bring into this
competition
she competed at the World Championships
in Barcelona last year just missed out
on a place of the final edition 13th in
the semi final 21:40 there with the
preferred by
last year
make her holy from the United States
seven after two rounds it's back down
well it's another disappointing sentence
schools their 360s
de Oliveira
the Brazilian girl with the fancy
drivers for a potential metal
[Music]
it's all about eradicating any
unnecessary mistakes in this first round
before big these lower tariff dives as
cleanly as positive just like he's just
looking away they're losing the extra
splash we said it was red instead of 80
[Music]
see a leader
it's from Belarus
understand forward somersault here got
to show she's in control of fact
gymnastic maneuver to the judges before
she releases but for the push-off to see
how much hard she can get
well there was a long spring off the
platform there it was a bit more than a
fall straight through into the dive
so hard to hold it there and then get
raunchy 138 points go down as far as six
so they kind of lead a today's bill - no
I feel like Pike's worth 1 point 8
the junkies got a good side all of you
there's four on one side three on the
opposite seen all those high chairs just
as she goes through the wheels are there
a lot of water splashed on the entry
which leaves a bad impression that she
underscores 30 to 40
Molly Carlson this diver at the games a
very peculiar champion last year Mike
don't fight
compete at the 10 meter eventually
qualifier falling away they're all entry
but still scoring up 30 50 which is a
decent return 17 years of age he is
formed
[Applause]
the driver indeed only reaching for the
water
again he clawed two big bolts in that
3:9 series of the thief pretty low
couldn't already retained which
unbelievable on the very first day of
competition
[Music]
no show ye God Malaysia
quite a busy southern completing at the
Commonwealth Games
they sure had a very strong gaze in
Glasgow where the games weak Glasgow the
target was actually at the whole world
fall in Edinburgh dfi Malaysia had an
excellent competition with Abed polygon
from the women who've been the stronger
internationally 37.5 stare back won the
half somersault with half a twist
a little bit more movement in that dive
for the crowd to adjoint lives with a
twist and out we are reaching it's all
about swapping that rotation once you
get into the somersault flip tidally
executed by Maha 2004 points
[Music]
hello Kalani has made a very good start
50 points with her second dive did you
do this reverse tie
no coach was telling me that if she
could finish at the top six that would
be a very good return for her
looking out for the water there but not
really seeing the dive all the way
through the entry and down into six
point five 2705 just what is goodness
her second dive 20 beans have about a
loft Lhasa will have serious metal
ambitions in this competition but she
want to make sure she gets these first
four dives which will count in the final
absolutely right
quickly out into the entry position to 8
to the 7.5 still more to come
[Music]
so after three rounds
whooshing Bing has really started to
open up a lead they have one four five
two one two seven down the bottom is
always a fairly substantial spread of
marks from 145 to 97
it's all about putting together a
program especially today with 8 dives to
get through 5 is the ball in senior
competition it's all about keeping the
big mistakes
keeping the double bogeys off your card
to make a golfing analogy it's all about
consistency and then hopefully pulling
out the big points water really matters
kind of guys not Schlick reverse dive
[Applause]
you get some height off a platform
[Music]
gonna get nicely on entry at the
position 3:17 raesha
laid the wholly from the United States
the drink-driving tradition going back
through various verse 9 point
all right so many divers she used to be
involved here gymnastics and mr. blow a
hockey ice hockey to them
the only five is her score there
we made a Oliveira package seventh still
waiting for a bit of a show from the
Brazilian girl the first time 1.94
tariffs remember that was a lot nicer
sounding dive
very clean entry
quickly through that
but this will be posted in OIT
let's see Aida pizza from Belarus
it is miss dolly liked
we get onto the wall complex dives there
is a lot more to appreciate what's going
in a lot more to see what goes wrong
exactly
and wait these competitors from arriving
in those who came with the rest of the
team very pleased to finally get into
their competitive destroyed
PES belt alone of Colombia 11th place
after three rounds
all the way to the left you get a
different perspective of the judges were
we're looking from that camera angle of
course
great shape sterling the scores
[Music]
mati Carlson from Canada he gloated stop
Thunder Bay where they really take it to
her international cook completely went
to pieces
heart goes out especially the gunk
divers Darby but it doesn't go right it
really doesn't go right at all you can
see that she just lost control of back
through the air and you know that Paul
was 20 to 18
hope that behind you
[Music]
we're full of wonder half somersault one
twist 2.1 she does have the most
involved
Horace tariff program of all the
delivers responding there because we've
just started to see the first signs of
complexity in the diving
so elegant relaxed the light of the way
they coded on it three nines again going
right across the board
boy Keithley takes a copy
[Music]
je from Malaysia 16 year old
the feeder
ranking of 38 for all these girls do
never feel irenka you need to be in the
senior competition
very slight
aging divers are naturally very elegant
into the water you get to the main you
see the different body shapes can make a
difference to 87.5
back to the reverse stolid piked here
and then stead of officially my back
towards the board happens to be out away
from it
tidy nicely completed 7.5 40 to 75
pretty consistent with their marks a
little bit oh geez they kelloggi the
products have a great second I scored 50
points it's got a pike wonder half
somersault with half a twist you try to
get back to that started third so far
very start
we're taking the whole victory
[Music]
it's pretty decent
suck the hops out but then look at the
back 25
welco also starting to get into her
competitive drive Armstead forward
somersault
this is 1.9 up into that kidnap stick
position
it's to hold it show control get you
those good slippy push off with Mack
fall
[Music]
that's where the power comes in which is
pronounced in quite a lot of these women
to have that real arm strength to push
out from that platform you get to some
of the big lads the Timmy tee you'll see
a little bit more what I mean the 4560
is still a nicely executed guide it's
been fairly consistent we've got the
Lovett Eric dives out the way boom shake
Pete really is showing what she could do
Malaysia of Mexico seasoned performers
started to show there as well
around pi now we start to get going this
is where the dives become a lot more
complex got to impress the crowd what
will go wrong together because law sleek
with an inward toward a half somersault
hiked this is worth ten point eight
she's fish of the ones restricted
dollars
long way to the top of that position on
the platform
she will have a trigger
[Music]
they did that dive
successfully completed 53:20
Grisha leader Mahoney reverse to live
off Saab assault 2.8 Vitara here
cheetos had a couple of years on the
feeder circuit so knows what the
pressure is like a see through the
somersaults
[Applause]
it's all about controlling that spin
speed in the Tuck position there I have
to try and put the brakes on get into a
good entry position six
Ingrid de Oliveira back to the valve
somersault one half twists up to 3.2
with the degree of difficulty for the
Brazilian girl
don't you have a problem just putting
the brakes on that dive
through the twists
the tiniest of high positions and a
rather heavy entry
[Music]
six points for my five counting there
Karina fits up in the turn a somersault
2.8 is her first actual dive all the 16
year old from Minsk in Belarus
of course the the RT is getting through
your somersaults in enough time to give
you the room to open out into a good
clean entry position she came up a
little bit short in that cook your spin
speeds of course the harder it is to for
the brakes of really getting through it
the right proportions therefore halves
3780 tonight of Columbia she knows it
back to the half somersault with half a
twist hiked the degree of difficulty a
more modest two point six
the computer space who lay audience for
that one
attended opening up into the position
just about completing it to be hurried
Carson young because 2:16 next week
tempering experience for them that's
what these games are really about
top-level experience all through the
half service or 2.7 where she was very
quick through her spins in the Tuck
position that didn't really have the
control it needed to deal with it
enthusiastic put me through then it
starts to get a bit of Tidy towards the
end
every 35 10
till top of the pile reshaping
over three and a half sub assault 3.0
he really is showing her pedigree very
early on in this competition
who's nothing away at the top there
quickly look up quickly cheers to that
summer says great position lovely entry
absolutely vertical 9.5 that is to died
so far in here 8550 that is
[Music]
je has to follow that back totally out
of range they stuck out all the boards
to be ready to die all three the half
somersault their fight 3.0 for the 16
year old Malaysian girl
I retracted driver very good right
position
judges liked it from an 8.5 read account
7350 and really feel this competition is
beginning now
I'm sick and after the limited
dives she's now got a fool through the
half somersault it's 2.7 tucked position
here really get through the rotations in
time to get the entry position she might
have wanted
right off the platform
reaching for it and still continuing the
movements of the rotational movement on
entry that keeps her down to about 50
right Kibaki prob answers to get you so
far a lot of international experience
[Applause]
[Music]
- driver in the shape so she goes
through the air relaxed on entry
straining their 5405 the synchro silver
medalist from London 2012 completing
this fifth round with Aiden inward three
and a half somersault three point two
Gately was the point ease upright as
ideal
even as consistent as we might have
expected 62 46 fives
well the competition has started
properly and moon-shaped ping again
increasing her lead at the top blow from
Malaysia doing well Molly Carlsen
bringing up the rear at the moment
remember these dives won't count in this
evening
not used to watching diving on a regular
basis he will have realized by now that
in terms of cracking on through the
competition girls are always on the next
level of the platform stairs ready to
perform so we're into six of eight dives
now gonna try not slick from Ukraine who
is back in fifth position for the 18
year old from Kiev
gather with a towel on the end of the
platform there it gives some of the
divers more confidence when they run
towards that platform that they're going
to get the right rim
a little bit untidy there and the bark
is doubt of the six five six fifty eight
fifty
raesha late Mahoney ate after five
rounds from the girl from mutant in
Massachusetts you'd have to have Tracy
Byrd her coach out here with her all the
delivers quite that lucky have the
international coaches look after them is
the three and a half somersault the
garbage were 3.2 but she seemed to have
a problem again putting those brakes on
stop eating the rotation is getting into
the upright position into the Tarkin
just running out of room really 5:48
points there for ratio
the Oliveira separate after five rounds
arm stand back double somersault one and
a half twists usual positions get up
into the arms don't coming into the side
angle they're quickly up into it though
show the judges you're in control look
for the push off
hold
couldn't really complete all she wanted
to get through in time for the correct
entry through the twists
a little hurried you're getting a huge
fight off the board 59 20
Casa Vida fixer from Belarus was 12th of
a qualifying event all the hundred and
fifty points behind the winner so she
could just go back over to ground in
this competition she will have
progressed
right at all
coming out will be beer tree position
but just not finding it
and it's 2565 for that died in the
disaster
pays Beltran out as a forward through
the half Sava salt 3.0 the degree of
difficulty
danteeksi of the rotation
but no ice at the top of the died nice
speeding stare
but you can't control it 23:50
havilah where is her big heroin who was
at these games four years ago and now an
established international competitor
particularly strong the syncro events
arms down fact triple somersault huge
get up there
can't get out of it as well
they were really convinced but she had
that dive under control from the moment
she went into the on tone position
trying to get extra dry for the legs out
of it
[Music]
try to hold a decent entry position 5280
down in the column over the holes
the whole mood in the pool changes read
the local girl when she move
sorry wound shame ping steps forward it
with three and a half somersault 3.2
weekly overdue tiptoes absolute
composure
[Applause]
when he threw the spins reaches out and
a very good entry position
again run out of the top drawer 8640
he's looking in a different class no
Joey
from Malaysia 16 years of age looking
very nice so far
second place she's got a back to the
half somersault with half a twist this
one just worth 2.6
25 foot 347 he bows
we really hold
they rate these things regardless of
different stages with fair development
of course these seminars
I hope I'm staying forward double
somersault this is just 2.4
my team a balance there
got to show the judges she's got the
position under control now she has
so he pointed all the way
[Applause]
very interesting story around this
kitchen
neither don't have health or an indoor
pool in Egypt so could any training with
the weapons okay so winter was a bit of
a no-no for her 5218 she's got there
which is
La Colonia has been impressive in the
tune of of somersault perfect position
waste much time at the top of the
platform there before triggering into
her movement
[Music]
my position
one of these Djokovic's 6160 more
encouragement corner las casas Mexico
Stone Bank double somersault one and a
half twist three point two
boys territory in the competition candy
never got that one under control
hurried through the arm stand
expecting a bit more from suddenly her
pedigree but we're not really getting it
so far 28 points of each you can put
this behind her in the final but she
could do better
six rounds calm and romping away at the
top of the field in this preliminary
competition is wind shaping louver
Galatia and khalaby of France very
impressive
at the spread of point C's 2017 brigade
it's very current
[Music]
seven
$8.00
just pulled herself up to fifth and has
a reverse two and a half somersault
tucked 2.8 degree of difficulty
it'll be rushed
the
top of the platform there to her credit
tuck in a heavy entry 97 60
in August return
raesha made only eight of six rounds
going off to Stanford University later
in the year we would see in American
sports programs in many of these
American universities on stone back
double somersault one and a half twist
that's a nice starting position can she
capitalize on that
we're going to be fight off the platform
really or any extra and came up short in
the end didn't get the entry position 59
20 or the very can go
agreed the Olivera eighteen-year-old
Basilio
I'm competing with both lights here in
Nanjing for three-and-a-half somersault
the energetic good advert somersaulting
there the idea if accounting is to stay
as close to the platform as possible
that she was gonna be quite a long way
out into the water there and again never
really had the cost room to stop the
rotations ends up with 49 50
Jesse arena Pfitzner for Belarus
Peter the recently repaired Julia
championships at this height this
waiting this night oh she's got a silver
the previous year the European Junior
Championships quite recent
well cured the divers will see over the
next few days were competing there into
that homestead before the back damage
somersault with half a twist
thinking this together she's got it
under control now
difficult for the younger the divers not
had the chance to build up the body
strength the divers do a huge amount of
urgent work to give them an affinity to
get the extra height off the platform
and give themselves more room for the
dive to evolve down there for 250
today's Beltran of Colombia the only
10th place now has a back tuna half
somersault
2.9 like position
Dodge's regard that as a completely died
or not
[Music]
hike out of it
never really gone into any position to
make some sort of an entry well she
still gets children for 65 for it
it's thought that to get consistency
across your diving shed you cannot
afford a disaster it's going to take you
out of contention
Molly Carlson back two and a half
somersault
the Genji carbs
really complete to dive to any degree of
satisfaction
my position was decent enough but again
this is well short version 770 to
generate the speed through the
somersaults to give yourself time
pushing you up to say let's see how it
should be done on stand back double
somersault one half twist 3.2 for
whooshing
taking the loans risks lovely start
position
[Applause]
which is one of those starters and her
natural elegance is going to make her
look really good the matter
errors she came to me to the time injury
was the fishes come up with but still 81
loach ie has very good 16 year old to
carry on the 20 improvement made in
Malaysian diving the last 4 or 5 years
no more Bob stand back double somersault
1 on our twist here 3.2 the degree of
difficulty choose second
they know the big offense so far
[Music]
stop 7350 back to 6080 with that one
today I leave you to the valve
somersault just to continue the
conversation
I enjoyed with her coach they get to
training once twice a week
don't you work at Joyland working the
winter
it didn't really
get the whole job done through the air
there but Egyptian diving is starting to
progress and this is a very important
competition for them in terms of
encouragement
six is pretty 44 Baja
I come on he has been impressive
Olmstead back double somersault half a
twist two point seven the schedule only
has two two point eight that's the two
most difficult odds all she was never
really in control of that that they
world lost her when she actually got
into the dive it was quite tiny but I've
seen a little bit carried at the top
maybe big monster for that forty fifty
there after some good work today
that still full without really dazzling
all the thrill of a somersault here
here just a little short
very getting the entry position she got
aborted 5850
thing is possibly too young to be giving
a master class per foot or to describe
it any other way
below you to Mexico towards the top
there
go around together
final round of eight dives then gonna
come as no slick of Ukraine in the
forward two and a half somersault one
twist Pike position worth two point nine
two
[Applause]
encourage the busy morning these girls
because only 11 of them so the time in
between their dyes has been quite short
and then we also had eight rounds to get
through so it's been quite hard work for
them 56 55 to end today's efforts Organa
[Music]
raesha bladed Mahoney from the United
States
back one half somersault through the
half twists for her eight die
[Music]
[Applause]
well like all these competitors she will
be pleased to have got the first session
out of the way it's just a little bit
messy
59-42 finish up her
work England Oliveira from Brazil sick
in with three and a half somersault
tucked 3.2 is her concluding dive
really a lot a bit untidy towards the
end of there
is to avoid you of the format to have
eight rounds here this morning the first
four rounds score again in the final and
they've got four more dives so one of
the work has come this morning
fifty to eighty four Ingrid
[Music]
eleven after seven rounds for the girl
from Belarus
back two and a half somersault with half
a twist here
got the tiniest maybe they're getting a
little bit tired finding it difficult to
sustain their form all the way through
the competition which is absolutely
crucial
[Music]
4030 they're not the greatest
today's Beltran with her final dive
in wood through the half service all
tucked position
to
go into this final round
with me through
through the half somersaults
pulling away out of the vertical there
on a tree which helped to increase all
that splash and 48 points or Santa
Karolina
golly Carlson the fifteen-year-old from
Thunder Bay in Ontario Canada reverse to
the half somersault tact 2.8 to complete
her program to better ending for her as
well
don't say about died dies he's really
comfortable with they only have a
certain number to live their locker at
this stage of their development of
course
46:20 then
has been a superb demonstration by moon
champagne so far back to the half
somersault 1/2 twists
we'll be lucky girl from that gene
they'll be going home this crowd of
saying you've got to come along to the
final just to watch this girl because
like so many Chinese divers she looks
something a little bit special very good
hardly a flaw right from start to finish
80 points hammering out the big scores
all the way through all schools in the
80s for her
[Music]
though je has had a good first session
in the pool here second so great in the
ward comes to the final plenty to go
before then in the thrill of our summer
saw three point two to finish Kochi sign
off with an encouraging note yes
very nice very impressive so far
composed
meet quick from the air and clean into
the water 80 160 well done
sokku down from Egypt
we turn a somersault one twist my life
is a bit of Raleigh
may be completed to any satisfaction
quite a tall diver and we got a ludic
and the legs of quite an ADA there on
entry and that means it's down in the
pores were 34 18
another young woman to watch la kelloggi
of France attempted the qualifying event
remember back in March
she's obviously been putting in some
good work because
going to have delayed rather quickly the
table because it always suggests great
control
just how it hard work to keep the
standards right through the eight rounds
which is a lot
anaconda bleats the show
gradually quietly worked her way up into
third position which is a bit nearer the
fall guide for the Olympic silver
medalist back to the half somersault
Wonder half twist three point two
don't bring such a lot of pedigree into
this competition the youngest Olympic
medalist in Mexican history at London
15 then 17 now one of her best there six
between 40 to finish with
that is the end of the competition in
this preliminary round that they've
women's tell me the platform
whooshing ping absolutely superb from
Gunther whistle excellent
all qualify of course all come back for
the final they will have learned from
this first session
plenty to whet the appetite then we have
seen some encouraging performances but
also just what a test it can be at this
Olympic level for young divers can they
deal with the pressure can they produce
their really best form maybe their
coaches and they themselves will find
out over the next few days of
competition
what divert hands really shot
[Music]
so last round away in the diving
competition for a session of five days
of diving here in Nanjing and that has
wetted the crowds appetite I'm sure and
certainly all the whole of the local
support